<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<testimonials>
  <quotes>
    <id>1</id>
    <author>Chuck Norris</author>
    <department>- Martial Arts Champion</department>
    <quote>Chuck Norris' calendar goes straight from March 31st to April 2nd; no one fools Chuck Norris."</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>2</id>
    <author>Chuck Norris</author>
    <department>- Martial Arts Champion</department>
    <quote>Bill Gates lives in constant fear that Chuck Norris' PC will crash.</quote>
  </quotes>
    <quotes>
    <id>3</id>
    <author>Chuck Norris</author>
    <department>- Martial Arts Champion</department>
    <quote>If it looks like chicken, tastes like chicken, and feels like chicken but Chuck Norris says its beef, then it's friggin' beef.</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>4</id>
    <author>Mr.T</author>
    <department>- A-Team</department>
    <quote>It’s a little known fact that Mr. T was one of the Three Wisemen. His gifts to baby Jesus were gold chains and pity. </quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>5</id>
    <author>Mr.T</author>
    <department>- A-Team</department>
    <quote>Mr. T does not Leggo the Eggo, he eats the waffle and the toaster. Mr. T does not eat Toaster Strudel.</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>6</id>
    <author>Homer</author>
    <department>- The Simpsons</department>
    <quote>Marge! Look at all this great stuff I found at the Marina. It was just sitting in some guy's boat!</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>7</id>
    <author>Homer</author>
    <department>- The Simpsons</department>
    <quote>If you really want something in this life, you have to work for it. Now, quiet! The're about to announce the lottery numbers...
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>8</id>
    <author>Homer</author>
    <department>- The Simpsons</department>
    <quote>Heh Heh Heh! Lisa! Vampires are make believe, just like elves and gremlins and eskimos!
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>9</id>
    <author>Bill Cosby</author>
    <department>- Himself</department>
    <quote>A word to the wise ain't necessary -- it's the stupid ones that need the advice..
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>10</id>
    <author> Arnold Schwarzenegger</author>
    <department>- Senator</department>
    <quote>Money doesn't make you happy. I now have $50 million but I was just as happy when I had $48 million.
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>11</id>
    <author>Jack Handey</author>
    <department>- Saturday Night Live</department>
    <quote>It takes a big man to cry, but it takes a bigger man to laugh at that man.
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>12</id>
    <author>Jack Handey</author>
    <department>- Saturday Night Live</department>
    <quote>"To me, boxing is like a ballet, except there's no music, no choreography, and the dancers hit each other.
	</quote>
  </quotes>
  <quotes>
    <id>13</id>
    <author>Jack Handy</author>
    <department>- Saturday Night Live</department>
    <quote>Reading a good book is like the author is right there, in the room, talking to you, which is why I don't like to read good books.
	</quote>
  </quotes>
</testimonials>




